netdetective.net 2012-10-15

# NET DETECTIVE PRIVACY POLICY - HD Publishing Group, Inc.

NET DETECTIVE PRIVACY POLICY

[NetDetective.net](http://www.standard.netdetective.net/) and [HDPublishing.com](http://www.hdpublishing.com/) (collectively the "Site") is owned by HD Publishing Group ("Net Detective"). This Privacy Policy governs Net Detective’s ("we", "us" or "Net Detective") treatment of personally identifiable information that Net Detective collects when you use the Site. By visiting the Site, you accept this Privacy Policy. Net Detective values your privacy and is dedicated to protecting your personal information and providing you with Notice, Consent, Security and Access. 

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Tracking Technology: Net Detective logs IP addresses (a unique number assigned to every computer on the Internet) in order to improve security, analyze trends and administer the Site. We may track your movement within the Site, the pages from which you were referred, access times and browser types. We only use this information in aggregate to gauge the effectiveness of our Site, track information for statistical purposes and to improve the products and services we provide and do not link that information to you personally. We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third party sources for instance to verify your address or update your information and to create a "profile" of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information to information in the profile, in order to improve the content of the Site for you. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this Site. We use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our Site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s "help" file. Persistent cookies are used to differentiate users of our Site from subscribers of our service to customize the content of certain sections of the website and enable us to track and target the interests of our subscribers and to enhance the experience on our Site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some areas of our Site may be limited and you may not be able to use certain features of the Site. 

Net Detective adds to its online database (which is available to all members) information concerning and limited to member’ names, address, email, and phone numbers obtained through the registration process. If for any reason, a member does not wish to have said information included within the database they may contact us as set forth below in CHOICE AND OPT OUT.

Third Party Links: We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by our Site.

Advertisements: We may from time to time use various outside ad-serving companies to serve advertisements on our Site. In the process of serving advertisements, the ad serving companies may place a cookie in your browser's cookie file and may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this Site and other websites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. By delivering ads on our site, the ad-server is able to record what ads a user -- identified by the unique cookie -- has seen, and what pages the user was viewing when the ads were delivered. This web usage information is combined with other ad delivery information the ad-server has collected from your visits to our Site and other sites not affiliated with Net Detective. This non-personally identifiable information is used as part of the ad-serving process for reporting and to select and direct the ads you see online at our Site and other sites not affiliated with Net Detective.

Surveys or Promotions: From time to time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in sweepstakes or other promotions on our Site, which might be sponsored or conducted by a third party. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these promotions is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information. If there is a third party sponsor involved please make sure to review that party’s privacy policy. 

**USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We do not sell or market, knowingly solicit information from, or sell Net Detective to anyone who is under 18. We receive and store any personal information you enter on our Site or give to us in any other way. We may also receive information from you from other sources. We receive and store information you provide voluntarily on the Site. 

Vendors: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples might include sending e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links, and merchant processing functions. They may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 

Third Party Offers: We share personally identifiable information with third parties in order to have them send you special offers and promotions that we think you might find of interest to you. We will also occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, or promotions, which we have found that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use the information you provide in order to inform you of products and services that might be of interest to you, or to provide your information to third party companies please let us know by contacting us as set forth below in CHOICE AND OPT OUT.

Other Uses: We may use your personal information to contact you about the services on our Site in which you have expressed an interest, for example, if you have contacted customer service or made an inquiry.

Service-related Announcements: We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, or the delivery of a service is delayed we might send you an email, or if there is some service issue with something you might have ordered. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. 

Exceptional Circumstances: If the HD Publishing Group or any of its lines of businesses or affiliated companies, is sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, the relevant databases of Net Detective could, in whole or in part, be sold as part of that transaction. Therefore, information about the users of our Site, including personal information, will be disclosed as part of any merger or acquisition, creation of a separate business to provide the Site, our services or sale or pledge of our company assets as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company. Information about our users, including personal information, may also need to be disclosed in connection with a commercial transaction where HD Publishing Group, or an affiliate, is seeking financing, investment, support or funding. In such transactions, personal information will be subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy in effect when the information was obtained. We also may have to release personally identifying information when it is necessary to comply with judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, orders, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Net Detective’s users or others. 

NET DETECTIVE ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY WITH REGARD TO ANY THEFT, LOSS, ALTERATION OR MISUSE OF PERSONAL OR OTHER INFORMATION LAWFULLY PROVIDED BY NET DETECTIVE TO THIRD PARTIES, OR WITH REGARD TO THE FAILURE OF ANY THIRD PARTY TO ABIDE BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY OR AGREEMENT BETWEEN THAT THIRD PARTY AND NET DETECTIVE.

**CHOICE AND OPT OUT**

You may opt-out of us sharing your information with third parties, as set forth above, by contacting us by mail at HD Publishing Group, 1392 S. Woodland Blvd, Deland, Florida, 32720, Attn: Data Management Dept or email at support@hdpublishing.com. In addition, if you don’t want us to add the information we obtain from you when you become a member to our online database (which is available to all members) a request to opt out of that database can be submitted by you by mail with a notarized signature (to authenticate that the request is made by the member requesting such removal), specifying in detail the information that you provided that you wish to have changed or removed from our database. Removals will be completed within 15 days of receipt of said written request. 

**ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION**

If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information you provided to Net Detective is not correct, or should you wish to have your email address removed from our mailing list or contact information changed, please contact Customer Care at [support@hdpublishing.com](mailto:support@hdpublishing.com). We will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. We may still retain your information in our files however, to resolve disputes, enforce our Terms of Use, and due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our Site.

**HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**

We have security procedures in the storage and disclosure of personal information, which you have given us in order to prevent unauthorized access. Keep in mind however, that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 

Our Site may also contain links to other websites. Keep in mind that Net Detective does not control and is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of these other web sites. 

**NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**

The Effective Date of this Privacy Policy is set forth below. Please make special note of the Effective Date of this Privacy Policy. We may revise and update this Privacy Policy if our practices change, as technology changes, or as we add new services or change existing ones. If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy or how we handle your personal information or how we keep your purchases anonymous, you will know because the Effective Date of the Privacy Policy will change. If we are going to use any personal information in a manner that is materially different from that stated in our Privacy Policy at the time we collected such information, we will give you a reasonable opportunity to consent to the change. If you do not consent, your personal information will be used as agreed to under the terms of the privacy policy in effect at the time we obtained that information but you may not be able to use our Site or services in the future. By using our Site or services after the Effective Date, you are deemed to consent to our then-current privacy policy. We will use information previously obtained in accordance with the privacy policy in effect when the information was obtained from you.

**DISPUTES**

If you choose to visit the Site your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the laws of the State of Florida.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy contact us at [support@hdpublishing.com](mailto:support@hdpublishing.com) with a thorough description of your concerns or questions.

© 2009, HD Publishing Group.  

**Effective Date: April 17, 2009**
